http://www.desales.edu/privacy-policy

Graduate Studies
Master of Business Administration (MBA)
Master of Business Administration (MBA)
Tuition & Fees
Master of Arts in Criminal Justice (MCJ)
Master of Arts in Criminal Justice (MCJ)
Academic Calendar
Our Faculty
Info Sessions
Master of Education (M.Ed.)
Master of Education (M.Ed.)
Academic Calendar
Act 48 Credits
Info Sessions
Master of Fine Arts in Creative Writing and Publishing (MFA-CW)
Master of Fine Arts in Creative Writing and Publishing (MFA-CW)
Academic Calendar
Program Information
Info Sessions
Master of Science in Information Systems (MSIS)
Master of Science in Information Systems (MSIS)
Academic Calendar
Info Sessions
Master of Science in Cyber Security (MS)
Master of Science in Data Analytics (MS)
Master of Science in Nursing (MSN) & Nurse Practitioner (NP)
Master of Science in Nursing (MSN) & Nurse Practitioner (NP)
Choosing the Right MSN Program
Master of Science in Physician Assistant Studies (MSPAS)
Master of Science in Physician Assistant Studies (MSPAS)
Info Sessions
Doctor of Physical Therapy (DPT)
Doctor of Physical Therapy (DPT)
Continuing Education
Doctor of Nursing Practice (DNP)
Doctor of Nursing Practice (DNP)
AthleticsApply
Undergraduate ApplicationGraduate Programs ApplicationsAdult Studies ApplicationAccelerated BSN ApplicationVisit
Undergraduate Admission EventsGraduate Information SessionsAdult Studies Information SessionsAccelerated BSN Information SessionsRequest Info
About the Undergraduate ProgramAbout Graduate ProgramsAbout the Adult Studies ProgramAbout Accelerated BSNMake a Gift
Home
Privacy Policy
Important information about how we use online data collected on our website.
For information about student data privacy and the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), please visit desales.edu/registrar
DeSales University Online Privacy PolicyThe policy of DeSales University is to respect the privacy of all website visitors to the extent permitted by law. This online privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways in which this web site collects information, the uses to which that
information will be put, and the ways in which we will protect any information you choose to provide us.There are four types of information that this site may collect during your visit: network traffic logs, web visit logs, cookies, and information voluntarily provided by you.Network Traffic LogsIn the course of ensuring network security and consistent service for all users, the University employs software programs to do such things as monitor network traffic, identify unauthorized access or access to nonpublic information, detect computer viruses
and other software that might damage University computers or the network, and monitor and tune the performance of the University network. In the course of such monitoring, these programs may detect such information as e-mail headers, addresses from
network packets, and other information. Information from these activities is used only for the purpose of maintaining the security and performance of the University's networks and computer systems. Personally identifiable information from these activities
is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law.Web Visit LogsUniversity web sites routinely collect and store information from online visitors to help manage those sites and improve service. This information includes the pages visited on the site, the date and time of the visit, the internet address (URL or IP
address) of the referring site, the domain name and IP address from which the access occurred, the version of browser used, the capabilities of the browser, and search terms used on our search engines. This site makes no attempt to identify individual
visitors from this information: any personally identifiable information is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law.CookiesCookies are pieces of information stored by your web browser on behalf of a website and returned to the web site on request. This site may use cookies for two purposes: to carry data about your current session at the site from one web page to the next,
and to identify you to the site between visits. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may turn them off in your browser or may set your browser to ask you before accepting a new cookie. Some pages may not function properly if the cookies are turned off. We also occasionally use third-party companies for retargeting advertising; these companies install tracking code on our site which triggers our advertising, serving our advertisements to you as you visit other websites. These companies may also collect
and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third-party services).Unless otherwise notified on this site, we will not store data, other than for these two purposes, in cookies. Cookies remain on your computer, and accordingly, we neither store cookies on our computers nor forward them to any external parties. Unless
otherwise notified on this site, we do not use cookies to track your movement among different websites and do not exchange cookies with other entities.Information Voluntarily Provided by YouIn the course of using this website, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. For example, you may send us electronic mail (through a mailer or a web form) to request information, you may sign up for a mailing list, or
you may send us your address so we may send you an application or other material. Any personally identifiable information you send us will be used only for the purpose indicated. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff to
respond to the request and may be recorded to help us update our site to better respond to similar requests. We will not sell, exchange, or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to the extent required
by law. We do not retain the information longer than necessary for normal operations. Each web page requesting information discloses the purpose of that information. If you do not wish to have the information used in that manner, you are not required
to provide it. Please contact the person listed on the specific page, or listed below, with questions or concerns on the use of personally identifiable information.University
provide links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. We do not control these sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for their availability, content, or delivery of services. In particular, external sites
are not bound by the University's online privacy policy; they may have their own policies or none at all. Often you can tell you are leaving a University
by noting the URL of the destination site.If you have questions about this site, its collection of information, and its online privacy statement, please contact webadmin@desales.edu.
This site uses cookies to store information on your computer. Some are essential to make our site work properly; others help us improve the user experience.By using the site, you consent to the placement of these cookies. Read our privacy policy to learn more.
Accept
